A Guide to the Records of Jamestown 2007, 1986-2009
Library of Virginia
- Series III: Recordings - Audio/Visual - Historically Significant, 2006-2007., Extent: 2 boxes. (Box 57-58)
  - Through Our Own Eyes - Virginia State University (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Time for Kids (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Tribal Center Tour - Monocan Homecoming, undated. (Box 58)
  - TV News Clips (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - US Postal Service Jamestown Stamp (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Program (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Community Pull-Ups (CD), 2006. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indians: 400 Years of Survival (4 discs) (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indians: 400 Years of Survival Brochure (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indians: 400 Years of Survival CW (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indians: 400 Years of Survival CW (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indian Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indian Sponsor Poster (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Virginia Indians Visit London (VHS), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Virginia Roots: From Thames to James (CD), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Volunteer Images (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - WHRV Hearsay with Cathy Lewis (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - With Good Reason (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - World Forum on the Future of Democracy Video (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - York 225 Program (Sony DVCam), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - York 225 Program (Sony DVCam), undated. (Box 57-2)
  - Yorktown 225th Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
  - Yorktown Pics (CD), undated. (Box 58)
- Series IV: Project Documentation Files - Historically Significant, 2000-2008., Extent: 13 boxes. (Box 59-71)
  Series IV: Project Documentation Files documents commemorative productions and signature events created by Prosody Creative Services, Inc., an event marketing and management company based in Norfolk. Prosody was responsible for the Godspeed Sail, Jamestown Live!, America's Anniversary Weekend, and the World Forum on the Future of Democracy. This series also documents the various community programs held across the state and abroad.
  - Prosody Creative Services - Anniversary Weekend, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 2)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Anniversary Weekend Godspeed Sail National Teach-In - "A King's World," 2005. (Box 66, Folder 3)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Anniversary Weekend - Production Timetable, 2006. (Box 67, Folder 19)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Catering Information - Godspeed Sail, 2006. (Box 67, Folder 11)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Anniversary Voices", 2006. (Box 67, Folder 13)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Anniversary Voices" & "Ba-baaah & the Windigo", Undated. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Jamestown Live: Experience the Journey that Changed the World," 2006. (Box 67, Folder 15)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Journey of Destiny," 2005. (Box 67, Folder 16)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Journey of Destiny," "Meet the Presidents," & "Virginia Voices," 2005. (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "A King's World," 2005. (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Sign Up for the Voyage to the New World" Undated. (Box 67, Folder 14)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Virginia Voices," 2005. (Box 66, Folder 2)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Production - "Zachary Taylor," 2005. (Box 66, Folder 11)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Productions, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 9)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Commemorative Productions, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 10)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Communications Committee Meeting, 2005. (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Creative Advisory Group Meeting, 2005 March 2. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Creative Advisory Group Meeting, 2005 April 13. (Box 66, Folder 8)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Creative Overview of Four Signature Events, 2005. (Box 66, Folder 10)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Executive Committee Meeting, 2005. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Promotional Sail, 2003. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Sail & Landing Party Festival, 2006. (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Sail & Landing Party Festival - Weekend Session, Undated. (Box 66, Folder 7)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Sail Proposed Site Diagrams, 2006. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Sail Summary, 2006. (Box 67, Folder 8)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Godspeed Sail Technical Production Summit, 2005. (Box 66, Folder 15)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Jamestown Live!, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Joint Session - Creative Advisory Group, etc., 2006. (Box 67, Folder 17)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Media Tent, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 3)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Signature Events, 2004. (Box 66, Folder 12)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Signature Events - Budget Estimate, 2005. (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Signature Events - Budget & Notes, 2004. (Box 66, Folder 13)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Signature Events - Budget & Notes, 2004. (Box 66, Folder 14)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Television Special Draft Script, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Prosody Creative Services - Topical Conferences, Undated. (Box 67, Folder 1)
  - Signature Events - African-American - Black Expo, 2007. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Signature Events - African-American - Black Expo, 2007. (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Signature Events - African-American - Black Union, 2007. (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Signature Events - African-American - Correspondence, 2000-2004. (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Signature Events - African-American - State of the Black Union, 2006-2007. (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Budget Consult, 2002. (Box 70, Folder 17)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Credentials, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Credentials - Exhibitors, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Credentials - Media VIPs, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Guide, Undated. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Maps, Undated. (Box 70, Folder 8)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Planning, 2006-2007. (Box 70, Folder 11)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Script, Volunteers, Exhibitors, 2006-2007. (Box 70, Folder 12)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Staff Operations, Information Booth, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 13)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - Tickets, Transportation, 2004-2005. (Box 70, Folder 10)
  - Signature Events - America's Anniversary Weekend - TV Special, Undated. (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Signature Events - Commemorative Sail Early Planning, 2003. (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Signature Events - Commemorative Sail - Godspeed Sail, 2004. (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Signature Events - Commemorative Sail - Godspeed Sail, 2005. (Box 68, Folder 3)
  - Signature Events - English Launch, 2006. (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Alexandria, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Baltimore, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 6)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Boston, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Boston, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 11)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Coast Guard/MENS Permit, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 12)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Landing Party, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 14)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Launch, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - NASA Display, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 13)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - New York, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 8)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Newport, RI, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 10)
  - Signature Events - Godspeed Sail - Philadelphia, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Signature Events - Jamestown Live!, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 19)
  - Signature Events - Journey Up the James - Fact Sheet, Planning, 2002-2007. (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Signature Events - Journey Up the James - Marketing, Sail Committee, 2004-2007. (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Signature Events - Journey Up the James - Ports, 2003-2007. (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Basic Information, Fan, Program, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Booklet, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Final Report, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Marketing, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Media Report, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Planning, 2002-2007. (Box 71, Folder 1)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Planning, Fieldwork, Themes, 2003-2007. (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Press Release, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Program Elements, 2005-2007. (Box 71, Folder 2)
  - Signature Events - Smithsonian Folklife Festival - Reception, 2007. (Box 71, Folder 10)
  - Signature Events - The World of 1607 - Basic Info, Press Kit, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Signature Events - The World of 1607 - Exhibition Catalog, 2007. (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Signature Events - World Forum on the Future of Democracy - Binder, Undated. (Box 71, Folder 11)
  - Signature Events - World Forum on the Future of Democracy - Delegate Packet, Undated. (Box 71, Folder 12)
  - Signature Events - Yorktown 225th - Other Events, etc., 2006. (Box 68, Folder 17)
  - Signature Events - Yorktown 225th - Overview, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 15)
  - Signature Events - Yorktown 225th - Planning, 2003-2006. (Box 68, Folder 16)
  - Signature Events - Yorktown 225th - Symphony, 2006. (Box 68, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - AAA, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Contest, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Garden Clubs, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Governor Kaine - 1st Garden Event, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Historic Triangle Beautification Committee Meetings, 2005-2007. (Box 60, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Pamphlet, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2002. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2004. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2005. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2006. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2006. (Box 60, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Planning, 2007. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Promotional Seed Packets, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's Anniversary Garden - Vendor Kit, Undated. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - America's First Freedoms, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Ancillary Events, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Banners/Flags - Price Quotes, Design, Order, Undated. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Capt. John Smith 400 Project, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Chairs Meeting, 2006. (Box 59, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Chairs Meeting, 2007. (Box 59, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Chesapeake Bay Gateways Network, 2007. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Children of the American Revolution, Undated. (Box 61, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Abingdon, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Alexandria, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Alleghany County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Altavista, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Amelia County, 2006-2008. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Amherst County, 2006-2008. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Appomattox and Appomattox County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Arlington County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Augusta County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Bath County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Bedford and Bedford County, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Berryville and Clarke County, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Big Stone Gap and Wise County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Blacksburg, 2006-2008. (Box 62, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Blackstone National Alumnae Association and College Archives, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Bland County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Bluefield, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Botetourt County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Bristol, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Brunswick County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Buckingham County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Campbell County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Caroline County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Carroll County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Centreville, 2007-2008. (Box 62, Folder 25)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Charles City County, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 26)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Charlotte County, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 27)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Charlottesville, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 28)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Chase City, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 29)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Chesapeake, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 30)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Chesterfield County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 31)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Christopher Newport University, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 32)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Clarksville, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 33)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Colonial Beach, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 34)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Colonial Heights, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 35)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Culpeper, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 36)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Cumberland County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 37)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Danville, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 38)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Deltaville, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 40)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Diamond Hill Historical Society, 2006-2008. (Box 62, Folder 39)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Dickenson County, 2006-2008. (Box 62, Folder 41)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Dinwiddie County, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 42)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Dumfries, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 43)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - East Lindsey District, Lincolnshire, UK, 2004-2008. (Box 62, Folder 44)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Eastern Shore, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 45)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Emporia, 2003-2008. (Box 62, Folder 46)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Essex County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 47)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Ewing/Lee County, 2005-2008. (Box 62, Folder 48)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fairfax, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fairfax County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Falls Church, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Farmville, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fauquier County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fincastle, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Floyd County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fluvanna County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fort Belvoir, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Franklin, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fredericksburg, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Friends of New London, Inc., 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Front Royal, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Fulgham-Fulghum Family National Association, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 14)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Gadsden County, Florida, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 15)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Galax, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 16)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - George Mason University, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 17)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Giles County, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 18)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Gloucester County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 19)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Goochland County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 20)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Graves Mill, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 21)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Gravesham Borough Council, Kent County, UK County, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 22)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Greater Williamsburg Women's Association, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 23)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Grayson County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 24)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Greene County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 25)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Greensville County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 26)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Groveton, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 27)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Gum Springs, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 28)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Gwynn's Island, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 29)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Halifax County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 30)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Hampton, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 31)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Harrisonburg/Rockingham County, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 32)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Harwich County, UK, 2006-2008. (Box 63, Folder 33)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Herndon, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 34)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Highland County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 35)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Historic St. John's Church, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 36)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Historic St. Luke's Church, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 37)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Hopewell, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 38)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Isle of Wight County, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 39)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - James City County, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 40)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - James River Plantations, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 42)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Jamestown, Colorado, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 41)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Kilmarnock County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 43)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - King and Queen County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 44)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - King George County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 45)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - King William County, 2004-2008. (Box 63, Folder 46)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - La Crosse, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 47)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Lakewood County, 2007-2008. (Box 63, Folder 48)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Lancaster County, 2005-2008. (Box 63, Folder 49)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Leesburg, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 50)
  - Virginia 2007 Community Programs - Community Program Files - Lexington, Rockbridge County, Buena Vista, 2003-2008. (Box 63, Folder 51)